Hello, my friends.
And welcome to exercise number 18 in time complex.
So we are asking to find the time complexity of this function called but the two parameters and A and
B and find the modules of two of the division of between them a modular to.
OK, so a Module B would be the result of this mod function.
OK.
Post the video and think about this.
What is that time complexity?
As you solve more questions and exercises as you are, as you advance in their career and advance your
algorithm and problem solving skills, so.
I help you solve this and commend it in the comments below.
Let's try to solve it.
If be less than or equal to zero, we have to return minus one.
OK.
There is no else block for this.
I told you in the general concepts that if else and the conditional statements, we took the worst one
between them.
OK.
If be less than zero to 10 minus one, no dependency on the imports, so it would be off one end division,
we are declaring a variable.
They've equaled a less than B or sort of a divided by B.
So this would result in a constant operation of what we are just dividing a of a b.
OK.
And we are declaring a variable there a slash b no return.
A minus five times B.
This would be resolved in all of form because we are not depending on anything.
OK.
We are just making an operation.
And like subtraction, operation and product.
A bridge of constants.
OK.
So A and B a year minus times b, we return the models.
This one of one and one.
This will result in 04.
OK.
It's very simple question, but it is an interview question.
So we should result there.
We should mention it, and we should cover all of these results.
All of these big O notation in order to get ready and crack that big.